Yeah! All right! We made it!
Yeah, we did! That was great!
We must have gone five kilometers today!
When we first got started, I thought it'd take years.
But at this pace...
Hello, Masadora!
For the second time!
Okay! Now, let's head right back to where we were.
Again?
Hold on to the front of the sky at the top of the一下子
四een目鳴っても湧き瞳ぐ
天使の微笑みで連れてieme
天使の微笑みで連れて перем rats
孤独でもひとりじゃないさ
You can smile again
You can fly away
I am from behind the scenes being there haha
Look who doesn't feel shorter
You learn how big you are
Actually, I cannot go off do which end
I can't help the design children
You'll never get enough of something
Next, we're going to work on collecting monster cards.
You now have the physical strength to beat every enemy you might encounter here.
But what you lack is strategy.
The ability to think while you're on your feet.
And that's important whenever you're fighting an enemy.
So, combat analysis skills.
Wait, combat analysis skills?
Now, I won't be handing out advice freely.
So, you'll have to try and figure out your own methods for defeating the monsters.
Still, all things considered, the game's creators were actually pretty smart.
It's programmed so that the player is guaranteed to get stronger as they progress.
And most likely, it's all for the purpose of making that child stronger.
One must battle a wide variety of enemies in Nen combat.
The most critical of all the battle skills is the ability to think quickly.
You have to get used to thinking constantly until your thoughts are tied to your reflexes.
This game is a training regimen to help you achieve that.
The hardest monster to defeat in this area is the Bubble Horse.
Once they clear that, they'll have completed the second phase.
That's who!
When it comes to analysis and physical strength, Killua has the edge.
But Gon makes up for it with his concentration and lightning-fast recovery speed.
Those two really make a perfect team.
Okay, now we'll begin training you in defense.
Hey, is that...
That's right, Gon.
This is the technique you've both been using.
Ten, Zetsu, Ren, Hatsu, and Gyo are all combined in this single technique.
Called Ko!
You focus every ounce of your aura into one part of your body and then attack.
This method gives it far greater power than your regular attacks ever could.
I'm going to attack you with my fist.
And you must block my attacks by any means necessary.
No dodging allowed.
Figured it out yet?
That's right.
If you use your aura to block normally, you'll take considerable damage.
So instead...
We should use Ko as well.
You're half right.
Ko versus Ko.
Unless the disparity in power is too great, a well-executed block will protect you.
But if your opponent hits you in a place where you weren't using Ko, you'll be destroyed.
Then we should use Ko on our entire body.
But it sounds contradictory.
Exactly.
This technique combines both Ten and Ren.
It's known as Ken.
You defend yourself by shrouding your body in much more aura than usual.
It isn't as strong as Ko, of course, but it's infinitely more practical.
Gon, use Ren, please.
Ken is sustaining that for a long time.
Now protect yourself from my punch, if you can.
It's so slow.
You let your guard down when you saw how slowly I was moving.
If you'd stopped using Ken, I would have crushed your face.
That's the power of Ko by itself.
When I add the speed and power packed into a normal punch, it gets stronger.
Many times stronger as a matter of fact.
Perhaps even dozens.
I'll start by going slowly.
And don't expect a warning.
Keep using Ken and try your best to withstand my attacks.
That was almost a full two minutes.
I had no idea that trying to maintain my Ren for so long would be so hard.
If you want to stand a chance, you'll need to be able to sustain Ken for at least 30 minutes.
Alright, we're done.
Time to practice Ken.
Good. That's 30 minutes.
You've certainly gotten a lot tougher over the past month.
The number three!
Ding!
Kilowa by a hair.
Gon, give me a thousand push-ups.
Alright.
Today, we'll begin actual combat training.
Ken!
In your current state, both your attack power and your defense are at 50, which means that at this point, if you were to fight each other using Ken, you wouldn't be able to cause much damage at all.
So what do you do?
We use our Ko!
No, you dummy!
What if he hits you where you're not using Ko?
What then?
We use Gyo.
Correct!
So with an even split, right at the moment of attack, shift offensive and defensive power of your right fist to 70, and the rest of it to 30.
And then, you can use Gyo to change the ratio of power to suit your situation.
This is called Ryu.
Now set your right hand to 70 for offense and defense, and the rest to 30.
It doesn't have to be precise.
Just try it out.
Left foot to 80, your body to 20.
Now head to 60, your body to 40.
Do this for 30 minutes three times a day, along with your current training regimen.
Also, we'll begin sparring.
Use Ryu just as I taught you.
Start out by trying it slowly.
When you're on the defensive, you'll want to determine your opponent's attack power before defending with Ryu.
With that said, begin!
I'll go first, okay, Gon?
Right foot, 55 on both fronts.
Right foot, 60 offensive and defensive.
I think.
Left hand, 60 for both.
Right fist, 80 offensive and defensive.
Left elbow, 80 offensive and defensive power.
If they keep this up every day for two months, they should be able to fight easily at full speed while still using Ryu.
And then, the final phase begins.
Okay, break time!
Thank you for sparring with me.
Ops!
It's been two weeks.
You've made a lot of progress.
It looks like you're both ready to enter the final phase of training.
Final phase, huh?
Yes.
You'll start training in individual categories.
Three!
Bingo!
That was a tie.
You can train exclusively in your own category.
In the case of an enhancer, you'll focus on your enhancer skills while training in transmuter and emitter abilities equally.
That'll help you master your own category faster.
Nine!
Well done!
Another tie!
Really good job, Kilua.
Yeah, same to you.
Now let's get started.
Ops!
We'll start off in the enhancer category.
The first exercise is breaking rocks.
And I want you to break them like this.
Smash a thousand with a single stone in a day and you'll clear the level.
Now begin!
This is pretty tough.
I'm just changing the stone's offensive and defensive power to a hundred right at the moment of impact.
But I can feel my nen getting weaker as I go.
Oh, I crumbled.
If the stone in your hand breaks, it's over.
Dammit!
I messed it up!
What are you talking about?
You were actually doing well.
Okay, let's do a transmuter exercise next.
Now, now.
Don't be so hasty.
You're only allowed to train in one category per day.
A six!
Right!
Tie it again.
Really?
We keep tying.
All that means is that you're both growing a lot more accustomed to using Gyo.
But it's not any fun if there's no winner.
Then let's decide with rock, paper, scissors.
And the loser has to do a thousand push-ups, okay?
Fine by me.
Now show me rock!
John can bone!
I win!
Dammit!
Hey, boys.
Have you heard that this game is based on the martial arts?
Paper represents a palm attack to the organs.
Scissors represent a finger jab to the vitals.
Rock represents a punch targeting muscle and bone.
A long time ago, martial arts were called jokin or evil fist
and considered so destructive that they were completely forbidden.
But masters were able to continue their training by pretending to play.
And that's how many people think jokin or rock, paper, scissors first came to be.
Wow.
You're really old.
That's it!
The jokin!
Huh?
Evil fist!
Gentlemen, we currently have 133 specified slot cards of 90 different types.
And of course, it's all thanks to your tireless efforts.
Of the remaining 10 cards, we know the location of 7 of them.
They'll be ours before you know it.
But, Tescara's group is closing in.
They've obtained the same number of specified slot cards.
And now, the final hurdle will likely be a showdown against their group.
However, I believe we have more spell cards, and of much higher quality.
So, our victory is all but assured!
May I?
I have something to say.
These past five years have been so long, yet so fleeting.
And now, there's something that I feel I really need to share with you.
I am the bomber.
What?
The bomber?
Hey, wait.
What are you talking about?
Please, hear me out.
I've already planted bombs on each and every one of you.
You what?
How did you even do that?
Yeah, you're kidding, right?
Calm down and listen.
Oh, dear.
You've disrupted the proper sequence of my explanation.
This is my ability.
Little flower.
You see, I can blow up anything that I grab.
But, it isn't all that strong.
He's still alive, of course.
However, if the bombs on your bodies were to suddenly explode, you would die.
A bomb!
But where is it?
Listen up.
And I'll be more than happy to tell you how to disarm them.
Let's begin with how I set them.
That was simply by touching the place on the target I wished to explode.
And uttering a certain key word.
Which is...
Bomber.
It sounds like it was the Bomber.
Listen.
Beware of the Bomber.
To disarm the bombs, you must touch me somewhere on my body and then say the phrase,
I caught the bomber.
That said, don't forget about my secret weapon.
The little flower ability.
I can use it to stop anyone who tries to touch me.
You must be very careful when attempting to disarm the bombs.
That's all.
What's the matter now?
My other ability is countdown.
Why am I telling you all of this, you might be wondering?
That's the condition for arming the bombs I planted on you.
Then you.
We're just waiting for the day that all of the karts and members were gathered.
And now, I have a proposition.
I will trade your lives for the 90 specified slot cards you've obtained.
If you agree to my terms, then I will use an alternative method to simultaneously disarm all of the bombs.
Do nothing, and all of you will die when the counter reaches zero.
You should discuss this amongst yourselves.
I'll be waiting for you at Mr. Patera's old mansion.
And whoever comes must come alone.
Do you have a screw loose or something, buddy?
If we just catch you right here and now and disarm the bombs, it's all over.
It's you against us.
Do you really think we'll just let you walk away?
Relax.
If you get too excited, the countdown will accelerate.
I should have mentioned that the counter is linked to your heartbeat.
What?
Hook.
No!
I do hope that we meet again soon.
Leave!
On!
He escaped out of the game!
Hurry!
We gotta follow him!
Wait.
But if we leave, the spell cards in our binders will vanish!
So what do we do?
Just calm down!
Going after that guy would be foolish!
Did you already forget why we decided to team up in the first place?
Because none of us are strong enough fighters!
Does anyone here actually think we're powerful enough to beat him?
It's impossible.
He must be quite strong.
His nin abilities prove it.
If all of us decided to attack him together as a unified front, he could simply use Little Flower to stop us.
Damn!
We were getting so close, too!
To start, it's imperative that we come to a consensus.
Do we try to fight, or do we just hand over the cards?
Hand them over.
Please.
Do it.
I'm sorry, but Jispa is running out of time.
What a surprise.
I had assumed that Nyx would be the one to show up.
I'm surprised, too.
Thought Judah had company.
Sub and Bara.
They're the other bombers.
Now, I'll have to ask you to hand over your ring.
What's wrong?
I can't turn it over yet.
Thing is, we still haven't agreed.
And Nyx has a request.
He wants you to let us have the Angel's Breath card so that we can use it to save Jispa.
I refuse!
As it stands, neither side can win!
Huh?
You don't realize how hysterical they're all being right now.
If they can't decide in time and they explode, then you lose everything.
All the data in their rings.
You need me.
You can convince them.
Is that what you're saying?
Are you really trying to bargain with me?
Because when you sit down to negotiate, you have to demonstrate to your opponent just how calm and insane you are.
Hey, wait!
If you kill me now...
Don't worry.
If you kill a player outside the game and take their ring, their specified slots card data remains intact.
Well, someone has the cards, but I highly doubt that it's you.
I brought you a gift.
You won't get another chance.
Got it?
Leave.
Hand over the leave card right now.
I need to go, so hurry.
You're crazy!
Leave is a really valuable card, and we can't waste any!
All right, have it your way.
But if I don't come back here, you can't disarm all of your bombs simultaneously.
What?
Well, I'm also a bomber, so...
There are three of us.
Well, Genthrou's the main one.
The rest of us are basically his wingmen.
When the three of us join our right thumbs and say the key word, the bombs will be destroyed.
And that is the alternative method.
Whatever.
I'll take my time returning by traditional means, and you'll all be dead soon.
Wait! Hold on a minute!
Here, you can just take it.
Should have done that in the first place!
We'll need leave cards when the deal is made, so get three of them ready.
Got that?
Let's go!
A mere 12 hours earlier, Genthrou revealed himself as the infamous bomber, and a single boat attempted to invade the island from the outside.
So it does exist in the real world. This must be it Greed Island
Come share your明日を目指す 朝日に照らされた傷 笑い合って 終わることない旅を続けよう
向かい風としていながら それでも進む理由がある
だから友よ 置いてくためだけに生きるのはまだ 早いだろ
身につけたもの 抱え込んだもの 手放したとき 始まる何か
上手く生きてく レシピを破り捨てて感じるリズム そう僕らのやり方で
次の動画でお会いしましょう!